looka.com 2019-11-27

# Privacy - Looka

This privacy statement describes how Looka (“we”, “us”) collects and uses the Personal Information you willingly provide on our Web site: Looka.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personal Information and how you can access and update this information. Personal Information is information about you, that is not otherwise available to the public, that you willingly provide to Looka in order to use or pay for our services.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should first contact us at support@looka.com.

 **Collection and Use of Personal Information**

In order to facilitate the operation of our site and manage your account, we collect Personal Information from you. For trial and paying customers this information may include but is not limited to, your name, email address, credit card or debit card number, your zip code, your address and phone number.

Depending on the documents you create with our service we may collect Personal Information including, but not limited to, names of people you have personal or business relationships with, items you own or wish to transfer ownership of, financial matters, and personal accounts or account numbers with banks, financial institutions, merchants and vendors.

 **We use this information to**

– Fulfill your order  
– Send you an order confirmation  
– Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products  
– Respond to customer service requests  
– Send you a newsletter  
– Send you marketing communications  
– Respond to your questions and concerns  
– Improve our Web site and marketing efforts  
– Conduct research and analysis  
– Electronic and Web Browsing Information We Gather

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, browser settings, navigation through our site(s), referring/exit pages, and operating system. This information does not include Personal Information. We may use third party tools and analytical services to gather and analyze this information.

 **Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at support@looka.com.

 **Information Sharing**

We will share your Personal Information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your Personal Information to third parties.

We may provide your Personal Information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as credit/debit card processing, shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your Personal Information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your Personal Information as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

If Looka is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your Personal Information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your Personal Information, to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

To protect against fraud and misuse of our Website and Services, we actively analyze purchases, attempted purchases and use of the Website and Services to help us identify and block individuals suspected of misuse and/or fraudulent activity. We may use that information, in conjunction with our security partners and/or law enforcement to protect Looka’s business and systems, your Personal Information and assist those we reasonably believe may have been victimized by such fraudulent use of the Website and Services. We may share data (including, but not limited to, suspect payment information, email addresses, IP addresses, etc.) with our payment processors, and law enforcement, in an effort to reduce fraud. You consent to the provision of this information (including keyword search data) for such investigative purposes.

 **Third Party E-Commerce Solutions Provider**

Our shopping cart interacts with established PCI-DSS compliant third-party credit processing vendor(s) via SSL links. They host and collect your billing information for the purpose of processing your order and subscriptions. We use an established third-party vendor via SSL links to manage processing of refunds and updates of credit card and debit card numbers and expiration dates. These companies do not use this information for any other purpose. We do not store credit card and debit card numbers on our servers or systems.

 **Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include Personal Information.

 **Links to Other Web Sites**

Our Site may include links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Looka. If you submit Personal Information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies of any Web site you visit.

 **Security**

When we collect Personal Information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at support@looka.com

In order to make a purchase from us, you must use our third party credit processing vendor to finalize and pay for your order. Its privacy statement and security practices will also apply to your personal Information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

 **Additional Policy Information**

To review, correct and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at support@looka.com.

 **Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our privacy practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

 **Contact Information**

You can contact us about this privacy policy by writing or emailing us at:

Looka  
#400-116 Spadina Ave.  
Toronto, ON  
M5V 2K6  
Email: support@looka.com
